ILGWU Communications Department Photographs 5780/176 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Leaders on the Line (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Includes 1943, Helen Sample at a dance for returning WWII servicemen, 1995; Helen Sample at Paris Accessories, Allentown, PA., 1995; Leslie Fay strikers, 1994; Susan Nowroski and co-workers at Shamokin Industries, 1993; Workers at Triple AAA, 1993; David Skinner, 1992; Business agent Lucy Roberts with workers at Carla Gay, 1992; An activist team, Easton, PA., 1992; Congressman Robert Roe with ILGers, 1992; Photos on worker activists and the service they perform in shop, in the community and in politics, 1992; ILGers strike at Laflin plant, 1994
- Legislative Action (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Includes Cartoon "mocking Republicans" by Hugh Konopacki, 1995; Cartoon mocking Medicare, 1995; ILGers rally in Illinois, 1995; Unionists protest against NY Governor George Pataki, 1995; Capital Hill, Washington, D.C., 1988; ILGWU Legislative Director Evelyn Dubrow, 1994; White House Speaker Tom Foley and Rep. Marcy Kaptur, 1994; Dubrow at committee hearing on health care, 1994; Dubrow with Rep. Ron Klink, 1994; Dubrow with MN. Senator Paul Wellstone, 1994; ILGers with Congressman John Lewis, Atlanta, GA., 1994; ILG Business Agent Mary Bolden and unionist protest outside Federal Building, Little Rock, AK., 1994;Strikers at Rainfair, Racine, WS., 1993; Strikers at Domsey, NY, 1993; Dubrow with AFL-CIO economist John Zalusky, 1990; Rally during IUD conference, 1991; ILGers with State Assemblyman Sheldon Silver (D-Manhattan), NY, 1990; ILGers with Senator Frank Lautenberg, 1989; ILGers with Reg. Gary Ackerman, 1989; Dubrow with General Sec'y Treas. Irwin Solomon, Pres. Jay Mazur and Executive V.P. Daniels, (circa 1990's)
- L.E.T.T.E.R.S. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Includes Strikers outside Wal-Mart, Bristol, VA., 1986; Letters to Justice, 1986
- Local 10 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Includes Pres. Jay Mazur, New England Region director Ron Alman, Local 10 Manager Rich Rumelt, Edwin Berman executive board member, Sam Boccassini, local vice president, and Robert Stolarsky, president, 1995; Cutters, 1994; Manager Rich Rumelt & family, 1994; Members at graduation, 1993; Retirees club, 1988; Manager Israel Mechlowicz, 1988; Cutters show support for Michael Dukakis, 1988; Mechlowicz and Pres. Robert Stolarsky with 50-year honorees, 1987; Retirement planning seminar, 1987; Harry Greenberg, president of retiree club, 1986; Mechlowizc, Retiree Svc. Dept. Dir. Matthew Schoenwald with retiree club, 1986; Mechlowizc and asst. manager Semour Resnick, 1992; B.A. Jonathan Smalls, Pres. Robert Stolarsky, B.A. Jack Goldberg, Mechlowizc, Gen. Sec'y Treas. Irwin Solomon and B.A. Seymour Resnick, 1987; Mechlowizc, David London, Gayle Schwartz, William Berman and Sam Meadows, 1989; Local 10ers in Poland, (circa 1980's); B.A. Dave Caloia, 1991; Local 10 graduates at ceremony, along with Mechlowizc, Exec. V.P. Edgar Romney, Caloia, Maria Conchita Leung, of the Garment Industry Development Corp. (GIDC); Adam Freidman, director of GIDC, BA Carl Zavatteri, Smalls and Sid Belsky, teacher at Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT); Cutters present dues book, 1987
- Local 99 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Includes Local 99 members help with alcoholics, 1994; Unionists from Monette Casuals, Avenal, NJ, 1994; Sidney Gerstein, manager, John Huffman, executive director of the American Red Cross, Walter Stein of the union's Member assistance Program and Nestor Sabogal, director of labor relations with K-Mart, 1992
- Local 89-22-1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Includes Workers prepare Hillary Clinton's dress, 1993; Carlos Rivera, 1993; ILGers protest outside D.J. Sportswear, 1994; Strikers protest Leslie Fay, NYC, 1994; Point Blank workers ratify contract, 1993; Upstate NY Mgr. Judith Conley, Mgr. Barbara Laufman, NY State AFL-CIO Sec'y treas.; Elisha Amish and Ed Cleary, NY State AFL-CIO pres., 1993; ILGers who worked on Mrs. Clinton's dress, 1993; Point Black activists, 1992; ILGers picket Norma Kamali's midtown store, 1987; Workers at Camille's Fashions, NYC, 1987; Israel Mecholowizc, Sam Byer and Antonio Claudino, asst. managers, 1987; Members at the Unity House, 1987; Pres. Jay Mazur and V.P. Byer, 1987; Protesting outside Kamali's retail store, NYC, (circa 1980's); Graphic protesting Kamali's Fashions; Parsons Meares shop workers working on Broadway show customs, NYC, 1987; Celebrating the union's victory at Whittall & Shon, 1986
- Local 23-25 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Includes Members with banner, 1989; French filmmaker Louis Malle, Kingsway Industries, NYC, 1986; Asian Labor festival, NYC, 1995; Recipients of the 1994 Local 23-25 College Textbook Scholarships, 1994; Exec. VP Romney, 1995; 500 years of Puerto Rican culture celebrated, 1994; Labor Commissioner John Hudacs, Nick Unger and VP Romney, 1992; Local 23-25 art exhibition, 1992; Worker/Family Cultural week, (circa 1990's); VP Romney with retirees, 1990; Monks lead chant with music(circa 1990's); Traditional Chinese folk dance troupe, (circa 1990's); Sheldon Silver Assemblyman from NYC with ESL students, 1989; Rally at NYC's Herald Square, 1986; Kathy Andrade, education director of 23-25, New York State Labor History Association(NYSLHA) VP Michael Hirsch and Pres. Robert Wechsler, 1989; Exec. VP Edgar Romney, NYC, 1986; Kathy Andrade and 23-25 children celebrate Three Kings Day, Hanukah and Chinese New Year, NYC, 1988; Members at pre-natal classes, 1986; ILG business agent Alice Tse, 1986; VP Romney receives NYC Mayor Edward Koch's Proclamation in honor of the local's outstanding English as a second language program in Chinatown, 1987; Members and retirees celebrate Chinese New Year, 1987; Members children, 1987; Professor Philip Kelman of the Apparel Production Dept. at the Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT), 1987; Local 23-25 and Garment Industry Development Corp. (GIDC), 1988; Business agent Theresa Kang translates poster, 1991
- Local 66 - 32 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Includes Executive board authorizes strike, 1993; Members picket Esther Swimwear, Brooklyn, NY, 1994; Asst. Mgr. Robert Jordan, 1993; Majestic Shapes workers, 1993; B.A. Joseph DeAngelis with member, 1993; Members show off their art, 1991; Vice Pres. Anthony Sciuto, Joint Board Pres. Murray Hendler, ILGWU Exec. V.P. Romney and Manager Sam Fine, (circa 1980's); Members strike Tres Belle Lingerie Co., 1987; Pre-retirement seminar, with Yolanda Hernandez, Charlotte Immerman, supervisor of social workers, Social Security representative Sandra Ferrar, 1987; Members okay new terms, 1987; Manager Tony Sciuto with members, NYC's Roosevelt Auditorium, 1984; Ted Bernstein, director of the Benefit Funds Dept. with member, 1986; B.A. Elvie Franque with member, 1992; Mgr. Sciuto and Ass't Mgr. Bob Jordan with Chairperson Mary Steele, 1993; Members approve new contract, 1993
- Local 66 40 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Includes B.A. William Hernandez and Prontito strikers, 1986; Local members' children enjoy Puppet show and Easter egg hunt, 1986; Strikers picket Blue Star Webbing, 1986; Strikers picket The Belt Shop Ltd., 1988; Mgr. Ted Theus with member, Asst. Mgr. Tony Rosario and Theus with member, 1987; Mary McClean, Ted Theus, Jacqueline Felix, Gloria Hurley, Sarah Ellison, Diane Black, Adeline Hassan, B.A. Murray Kaner, Lisa Martin, Regina McClammy, Doris Matulewicz, Diane Robinson, Asst. Mgr. Rosario and B.A. Robert White, 1987
- Local 132 98 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Includes Members at meeting discuss truckers' pact, 1991
- Local 91 105 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Includes Workers at the Samantha Fashions shop, Staten Island, NY, 1986; ILGers collect clothes for the homeless, 1987; VP Sam Fine and Administrative Asst. Elvira Franqui, with employees of Matsil Bros., 1988; VP Fine at unemployment seminar, 1988; Members at Clothing Drive to Hale House, NYC, 1987; Members receive High School degrees, 1986
- Local 132 98 102 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Includes Mgr. Bill Lee with "ILGWU First Aid Team", (circa 1980's); VP Lee at truckers' meeting, 1994; Riddick Bowe with his ILG mom, 1993; Gyna Sykes, a shelter resident and chairperson of the NYC Advisory Council, 1994; Workers picket outside Book Covers Inc., 1990; ILG truckers, 1991; Workers at Vinylaire, Hillside, NJ, 1989; Workers at Au pair Industries, Moonachie, NJ, 1989; Workers at St. Gillan, Secaucus, NJ, 1989; Workers at Strauss Plastics Co., Newark, NJ, 1988; Members at the Universal Travelers Inc., Bronx, NY, (circa 1980's), Gyna Sykes, 1994
- Local 155 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Includes Strikers from Ultra Knitting with Local 155's, NYC, 1987; Strikers at Fiberdye, 1994; 155's and mine workers at UMW's strike headquarters in PA., 1993; Workers at Color Science, 1994; Ruth Groeneveldt, education dir. of Local 155, honored by the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, NY, 1992; Pres. Jay Mazur and Exec. Vice Pres. Edgar Romney with workers from Mademoiselle, 1992; Mgr. Norman Lewis with former Southland workers, 1992; Unionists demonstrate in front of NY State Supreme Court during Pymm sentencing, 1991; Strikers at the Quality contracting shop in Brooklyn, 1986; Students of Local 155's English class, Philadelphia, PA, 1988; Manager Norman Lewis, 1987; Christmas party, 1988; ILGers participate in an anti-apartheid rally at Mobil Oil headquarters, NYC 1987
- M.A.P. (Member Assistance Program) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Includes ILGers at Roxanne Swimsuit, Neptune, NJ, 1994; Irwin Solomon, general secretary-treasurer presents diplomas to staffers who completed Member Assistance Programs, 1991; First aid training with B.A. Rosetta Lyons and B.A. Roberto Gonzales, 1991; Walter Stein conducting first aid course, 1991; Members of Local 62-32, Deaf ILG members, 1990; MAP pre-natal seminar, 1989; Health care workers at the ILG Union Health Center receive CPR training, 1988; Spanish workshop on family relationships, 1988; Edward Cleary, president of the New York AFL-CIO, 1988; Union social workers from MAP leading a workshop in health fair, 1987; Union Health Center nurses test members during Health Fair at Unity House, 1986; Chinese members at conference on "Women at Work and at Home: A Survival Course for the 80's", NYC, 1986; ILGWU members at pre-natal workshop, (circa 1980's)
- Master Agreements (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Includes Exec. VP Wilbur Daniels, with VP Tony Sciuto and Sal Giardina, 1987
- Mazur, Jay (Pres.) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Includes Mazur at AFL-CIO conference, 1991; Mazur with Frederick G. Hingham, dir., Nationalities Service Center (NSC) president, Delores L. Howland, NSC asst. executive director, Mauzzafor Chishi, Irvin J. Sannit, Philadelphia Council, AFL-CIO, Joseph Fisher, ILGWU, Gabriella Labella, NSC coordinator of migration services, Margaret H. Lowzetta, NSC VP, Ted Moore, Exec. dir. United Way of Southeastern PA at the NSC awards ceremony, (circa 1990's); Mazur and Michael Dukakis, 1988; Mazur with AFL-CIO Sec'y-Treas Thomas Donahue and SD National Chairperson Bayard Rustin, NYC, 1987; NAACP Executive Director Benjamin Hooks, with Donahue, Pres. Lane Kirkland, ILGWU and Mazur, 1987; Mazur with Dick Wenner of the Fund for an Open Society, 1990; (A variety of Jay Mazur photocopied pictures), 1987
- Media Matters (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Includes - Working on the film, Roger and Me, Flint, MI, 1990; Summer Pick, Matewan, 1994; Summer Pick, The Grapes of Wrath, 1994; Roseanne Barr and John Goodman on the set of Roseanne, 1989; Jeremy London, Regina Taylor, Lilly Harper, Ashlee Levitch, Sam Waterson and John Aaron Bennett on the set of, I'll Fly Away, 1994; Sally Field as Norma Rae; Cover to Linda Barnes' novel Coyote; Eric Boghosian as Barry Champlain on the set of Talk Radio, 1989; Cover to Meredith Tax's novel Union Square, 1989
- Metro Organizing (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Includes Exec. VP Edgar Romney at rally with banner, (circa 1980's); Handing out leaflets in Brooklyn, NY, 1991; Describing work conditions to reporters, NY, (circa 1980's); Volunteers handing out union information, Brooklyn, NY, 1994; Local 17-18 workers at NLBR offices, (circa 1980's); Workers for Three Sisters, Brooklyn, NY, 1990; Advertisement, "We want a real union"; Protesting outside Labels for Less, NYC, 1988; Picketers watch nonunion workers do their jobs, Hialeah, Florida, 1988; [?] Hermanson address the existence of the new Metro Organization Dept., 1987; Pres. Jay Mazur discussing boycott of Soho blouses, 1988; Handing out leaflets; ILGWU has open house, Brooklyn NY, 1990
- Merger (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Includes ILGWU and ACTWU combine forces, with Pres. Mazur, Exec. VP Edgar Romney, Jack Sheinkman, VP Irwin Solomon, Bruce Raynor and [?] Loevy, 1995; 1910 Cloakmakers strike, 1995; Mazur and Romney with VP's Stanley Gross and Paul Winslow, Midwest, 1995; Mazur and Sheinkman at formal announcement of ILGWU/ACTWU merger, 1996; J.P. Stevens rally, 1970's, NYC
- Midwest (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Includes ILGers at rally against A.E. Staley Co., 1994; Local 187 at labor rally for Rainfair strikers, WS, 1991; Union negotiating committee for Kollcraft Products, 1991; ILG VP's Bonanno and Montenegro with Jerry Smolder, (circa 1990's); Colbert workers, (circa 1990's); Local 188 member Annie Meyers, honored, 1990; ILGers from Sportsman of Berlin, (circa 1980's); Midwest ILGers, 1990; V.P. Evelyn Dubrow and State Rep. Jan Schakowsky, Chicago, III, 1992; Rainfair hunger strikers, WS, 1991; AFL-CIO convention, WS, 1991; AFL-CIO rally, WS, 1992; Leafletting at Grainger, Chicago, Ill, 1991
- Midwest (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Includes Rainfair strikers, 1991; 1930 ILGWU baseball team, 1990; ILGers at the Industrial and Labor Relations school, at the University of Illinois, Champaign, 1994; VP Stanley Gross and signing the Great American Pact, 1994; Local 379 volunteering at the Salvation Army, 1994; Local 76 soccer team, 1994; ILGers at ILR of University of Illinois, 1993; Celebrating ILGWU/ACTWU union, 1987; ILGers celebrating Labor Day, Chicago, Ill, 1992; ILGers protesting against US-Mexico free trade agreement with banner, WS, 1992; ILGers in Chicago parade, 1990; Unveiling a "Fight Back" banner, 1987; Mort Weiner addressing joint ILGWU/ACTWU shop meeting, 1987; Midwest members at ILR of U. of Illinois, 1987; Local 1200 members have reunion, Decatur III, 1987; ILGers march to stop apartheid, Chicago, III, 1987; VP Lou Montenegro addresses Chicago "registration rally", 1987; Local 529 bowling league, Aurora III, 1986
- Midwest (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Includes - Sid Gerstein of NY addresses Local 336, Alsip, III, 1986; John Manis, asst. director of the National AFL-CIO Dept. of Community Services, Alsip, III, 1987; District Council No. 3 annual meeting, Lacrosse, WS, 1987; Members of local 171, Twinsburg, OH, 1988; ILG staffer Humberto Salina testifying before the Senate, 1988; Asst. Dir. of the Midwest Region, Mike Estigo, VP Lou Montenegro and Pres. Jay Mazur, 1988; Montenegro with Aurelia Pucinski, Democratic candidate for Chicago Circuit District Clerk, 1988; Charlie Stark, Midwest Regional Administrator Asst. swears in new officers, Chicago, III, 1988; Local 459 in parade, Mattoon, III, 1986; Strikers at Sewing Unlimited, Chicago III, 1986; Bill McMahon, manager of Midwest District Council #1 with Local 240 veteran, 1986; Local 459 members, Mattoon, III; 1986; District #2 officers, Terre Haute, IN, 1986; B.A. Humberto Salinas and chairperson at Clever maid Uniform in Chicago Gloria Hill at the Chicago Planning Commission, 1988; ILGers at the University of Illinois Champaign Urbana, 1988; Pres. Jay Mazur, VP Montenegro, Dist. #3 Council manager Don Kret and Amy-Dean political-education director, 1988; Workers at White Hall protesting pay cuts of Greene County Manufacturing, (circa 1980's); VP Montenegro administering oath of office to Chicago locals, 1986; Local 282 softball team, Oshkosh, WS, (circa 1980's); Workers at Monterey Mills ratify contract, Janesville WS, 1987; Workers at Advance Engineering join ILWGU, Franklin Park, III, 1988; ILGers march to protest grape boycott, 1993
- New England (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Includes Dye cutters, 1993; Recyclers Consulting Group (RCG) workers with CT Organizing Director Danny Perez, 1994; RCG workers with shop Stewart Raul Rinzon, 1994; ILGers from Mario Valente protest new leasing scheme, NYC, 1993; Elaine Glowacki, ex. dir., of S.E. Mass. Home Health Aides, Inc., 1995; Joint Board Manager Warren Pepicelli and Asst. Mgr. Helen Jue, Boston, MA, 1994; Workers at Futuramik, Hartford CT, 1994; Hartford City Councilwoman Susan Hyde, 1994; Workers at Church Street South housing complex, New Haven, CT, 1994; ILGWU joins community at Union Health Center, Fall River, MA, 1993; District Mgr. Nicholas Roussos and Rob Vitello, director of the U. Mass Labor Education Center, 1993; Mgr.. Pepicelli leading rally, 1993; Pepicelli at Chinese New Year party, 1993; Union workers help install Fall River bells, 1992; Workers picket Diamond Walnut, 1992; Workers at Fabrican, 1990; ILGers at parade, New Bedford, MA, 1990; Talk show host Joan Rivers, 1990; ILG graduates of the New Haven Central Labor Council, 1990; Garment workers square sign, 1990; Mass. ILGer named "driver of the year", 1989; Workers at Malden Mills, 1990; VP Ron Alman, New England region director, 1990
- New England (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Includes - Workers of Malden Mills, Lawrence, MA, 1990; Local 80, 24 & 178workers, 1991; Workers from J & J Mfg. 1991; VP Alman, Boston, MA, 1990; Workers at Archer Rubber, 1990; BA's Franco and Ferreira, 1991; ILGers at health fair, NY, 1991; ILGers remembering US service people, 1991; Servicewoman Geraldine Coleman, 1991; Local 75 self-defense course, 1986; ILG strikers from Cambridge Coat picket non-union Rosario Fashions, Boston, MA, 1986; Local 361, New Bedford, MA, 1986; ILGers picket Mackintosh, Brockton, MA, 1986; Local 178, Fall River, MA, 1986; Southern District Council, 1986; Boston Joint Board Business Agent Warren Pepicelli with members at Rimoldi Sportswear, 1987; VP Ron Alman with MA AFL-CIO president, Arthur Osborn, 1986; Michael Dukakis at TJ Maxx distribution center, 1987; Fire in Fall River, MA, 1987; ILGers distribute food, 1987
- New England (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Includes ILG art contest winner painting, 1987; Northern District business agents Gene Esposito and Elizabeth Jencunas, 1987; New England Patriot Tony Eason with ILGer, 1987; Members of Robby Len Swimsuit factory, New Haven, CT, 1988; Asst. Mgr. Jue and Mgr. Pepicelli, 1988; VP Alman, Local 178 president Eda Cabral, Dist. Mgr. Nicholas Roussos and VP Susan Cowell, 1987; Governor Dukakis with Susan Kim and Alman, 1987; Workers at Gemini Corp., 1987; Workers from locals 178-324. Somerset, MA, 1987; CT. BA Joe Vitelli, 1989; Workers from Tick Tock, 1988; CT organizing director Danny Perez with Uretek workers, Bridgeport, CT, 1987; Workers at A & A Sportswear, Fall River, MA, 1989; VP Alman at rally, 1987; Patriots fullback Mosi Tatupu joins striking ILGers, 1987; Workers at Robby Len, 1988; Strikers at Uretek Co., 1987; ILGers at Cardio-pulmonary Resuscitation (CPR) training, 1989; CT State Rep. Miles Rappaport at rally, 1986; Town Curtain workers protest unfair labor practices, 1987; Workers from API celebrate victory, 1986
- New England (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Includes Congressman Jim Shannon with Southern New England District Council, VP Ron Alman, Local 361 manager Cecilia Leshyk, Local 178 Pres. Ida Cabral and Nicholas Roussos, district manager, 1984; Congressman Gerry Studds endorsed by New Bedford MA Local 361, 1984; Members of Local 75, 1984; VP Ron Alman at Mass. Commerce and Labor Committee hearing, 1984; Local 178 50th anniversary dinner, 1984; ILGWU Santa hands Gov. Dukakis a "Buy American" leaflet, 1984; Chicago ILGers surround Congresswoman Cardiss Collins, 1984; Labor-management meeting at Zayres headquarters, 1983; Local 361 voter registration drive, 1983; ILGers promoting the union label at AFL-CIO convention, 1983; Local 313 delegates to AFL-CIO convention, 1983; VP Ron Alman escorts Boston mayoral candidate Ray Flynn through Lana Sportswear, 1983; Congressman Barney Frank presented with map of Fall River Factory Outlet District, 1983; VP Ron Alman testifies before MA legislative committee, 1983; Local 281 Executive Board members at statue dedication, 1985; Strikers at Avon Home Fashions, 1985; Strikers at Marie Dianne Fashions, 1985; Workers celebrate union recognition at Camden Tannery, 1986; Sol Chaikin, 1986; Ron Alman swears in Nathan Sandler, 1986; New Haven Mayor Ben DiLieto meets ILGers, 1986; Ida Cabral speaks at conference, 1986; ILGers at new plant groundbreaking ceremony, 1986; Ron Alman addresses meeting about strike, 1985; Sen. John Kerry, 1985; Rona Alamn outlines proposal to New England Sportswear Manufacturers Association, 1985; Frank Pereira retirement, 1985; Local 178 Easter Saels charity campaign, 1985; Sidney Sisselman escorted by police at strike in Pittsfield, MA, 1982; Paul Winslow made Central States Region director, 1984; Congressman James Shannon, 1984
- New Jersey (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Includes Local 134ers, 1986; BA Roberto Gonzalez, District Council Pres. Mary De Chiara, Asst. District Manager George Benson and District Manager Virgil Bavaro, 1986; Pres. Jay Mazur, Barbaro, Mildred Lippman, Eli Charne, Sol Goldberg and Paul Strongin, 1986; Dino Rinaldi, district manager of Passaic, NJ District Council, 1986; Workers from Albert Betesh & Sons receive backpay, 1986; State Senator-elect Gabe Ambrosio and Christine Kerber, manager of the Passaic District Council, 1987; Local 134ers, Passaic, 1987; Workers from Flora Fashions, 1986; ILGers leafleting, Newark, 1987; Giardina and Assemblyman William Shuber, 1987; Dinner for newly legalized ILGers, 1987; Dist. Mgr. Eli Charne with ILGers, 1987; State Senator Christopher J. Jackman, 1988; Charne and ILGers at Christmas party, 1988; ILGers join Jets & Giants on the Picketline, East Rutherford, 1987; Tom Scali, pres. of the Toms River Retiree Club, 1987; BA Luis Ramos along with ILGers who lost their home to fire, Saddlebrook, 1988; VP Giardina, Mamie Zarimba and Central District Mgr. Mildred Lippman, 1988; Assemblyman William P. Schuber, Giardina at Botto House on the 77th anniversary of the Triangle Fire, 1988; Workers at Pharaoh Design, East Newark, 1988; ILGers rally against apartheid, with banner, 1988; Carnival de Bergenline, 1988; Dist. Pres. Mary De Chiara and Asst. Dist. Mgr. George Benson, Essex, 1987; ILGers at Rutgers U for convention, 1987
- New Jersey (Box 11, Folder 2a)